A movie for everyone who wants to get married and stay single at the same time.
Walking and Talking is a comedy, drama, romance
film directed by Nicole Holofcener.
Just as Amelia thinks she's over her anxiety and insecurity, her best friend
announces her engagement, bringing her anxiety and insecurity right back.
Amelia, played by Catherine Keener.
Laura, played by Anne Heche.
Frank, played by Todd Field.
Andrew, played by Liev Schreiber.
Bill, played by Kevin Corrigan.
Young Amelia, played by Amy Braverman.
Walking and Talking is a 1996 independent film written and directed by Nicole Holofcener and
starring Catherine Keener, Anne Heche, Todd Field, Liev Schreiber and Kevin Corrigan.
The film is #47 on Entertainment Weekly's "Top 50 Cult Films of All-Time" list.
The film's soundtrack includes music from Billy Bragg, Yo
La Tengo, Liz Phair, and The Sea and Cake.
The film is notable for being the first
collaboration between Holofcener and Keener.
It was an international co-production between France,
Germany, the United Kingdom and the United States.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.